get ready to take your beauty and makeup
game to a whole new level because I'm
about to show you 12 amazing makeup life
hacks and DIYs that will change your
life your
Hal you
Hal
hey guys today I'm sharing with you 12
amazing makeup life hacks and DIYs that
will blow your mind and even if you're
not there into makeup I know you're
going to love these because they are
just so cool and fun to try so I hope
you like the video don't forget to
subscribe to my channel if you haven't
already and let's get
started hey party tonight okay see you
there
lips a these are so boring I know if you
really want to make a statement with
your lipstick this life hack is perfect
for you we'll be making amazing glitter
lips I'll show you a couple of different
variations and the first one is black I
don't have a black lipstick so I'm using
a black pencil eyeliner instead a bonus
hack right here use eyeliners as lip
liners and vice versa it's so much fun
trying new color combinations it's time
for glitter ah who doesn't love this
part make sure to use cosmetic grade
glitter since you're putting it on your
lips load the brush with glitter and
press it on the lips if the lipstick or
the liner that you used as the base is
creamy enough the glitter will stick on
nicely as you can see I have no Fallout
at all otherwise you can also use a thin
layer of lip gloss to help the glitter
stick in place there you go how gorgeous
are these glitter lips I think they're
absolutely perfect for any party New
Years Halloween or other special
occasions they look So Glamorous special
and just hands down gorgeous let's be
honest no lipstick could ever make such
a statement you don't have to go all
vampy and dark with black lips as I did
you can use any lipstick color here I
chose red I like the look when you match
the color of lipstick with the color of
glitter that goes on top so now it's
time to play with red glitter okay load
the brush with this sparkly Beauties and
gently tap it on the lips leaving a
beautiful glittery Trace look at this
Perfection come on now isn't this the
best thing ever just thinking about how
many different colored glitter lips we
can create makes me so excited about
life pretty embarrassing but I love
it
why it was my favorite don't cry we're
going to fix it well I'm not just going
to show you how to fix a broken
eyeshadow or blush instead I'll show you
how to make something way more awesome
out of it we're making a pink Galaxy
blush take a few old or broken blushes
and eyeshadows in different shades of
pink and purples put each color into a
separate pot I'm using a white purple
three pinky colors and a little bit of
glitter get a bit of alcohol into the
dropper and squeeze it out into each of
the pots where you have powders we're
doing this just to get that pasty
texture which is easier to work with
give all the colors a little stir set
these babies aside and grab an empty
blush container all we got to do now is
scoop small chunks of different colors
and place them randomly around the
container place a tissue on top of your
blush and press it down using a rounded
object this will make the blush nice and
flat remove the tissue let it dry for a
couple of hours and you're finished look
at this gorgeous pink Galaxy blush that
we've just created this is a great way
to recycle broken or old eyeshadows and
blushes if you want to just repair a
broken ey Shadow or a blush and leave it
as a solid color all you have to do is
squeeze some alcohol into the container
with cracked powder flatten it down and
leave to dry here I also made an ey
Shadow recycling my old pink purple and
blue Shadows how pretty it turned out
right what a fun way of making unique
and epic designs on your blushes and
powders I love my new lip gloss such a
pretty
color what why is there no color on my
lips why did I buy
you has this ever happened to you well
don't you worry girl because there's an
amazing hack that will make all your lip
glosses super pigmented and gorgeous
take a lip gloss and an ey Shadow or
loose pigment I'll use a pink eyes
Shadow to intensify the color of my lip
gloss scrape some of that shadow on a
piece of paper if you're using loose
pigment you can of course skip this step
grab the lip gloss and pour in the
eyeshadow powder I made a little paper
funnel to make that part easier if
you're having troubles getting the
powder into the lip gloss bottle a
toothpick or a kebab stick will come
very handy mix the gloss and the powder
together and boom look at how much more
pigmented gloss we've just created it's
hard to believe that these glosses were
the same only a minute ago our new lip
gloss actually gives a really nice pinky
color to the lips in contrast to the
original gloss which was transparent and
didn't do nothing at all the lip glosses
always look so gorgeous in bottles so I
often buy them when I put them on they
look completely transparent like where's
that pretty pink color at least now we
have a solution I love this Live Hack
this is the original lip gloss nothing
special and here's our pimp lip gloss
the difference is enormous and think
about how many different lip gloss
colors you can make I'll mix this pretty
silvery pink pigment with some
transparent lip gloss pour some of the
gloss into a little HT add a bit of
pigment or ey shadow in any color and
mix it up I seriously enjoy so much
making these makeup DIYs because they
are just so satisfying take a look at
this liquid silver wow so pretty we need
to make a Swatch to see if it's good
enough for the lip yep definitely let's
do this a pretty epic and a little crazy
lip color right I love
it I also made one using metallic pink
pigment I know I'm obsessed I want to
try all the colors having a transparent
lip gloss is so handy because you can
simply mix up any gloss color that you
want while getting ready put a blob of
clear gloss on the back of your hand add
a small amount of pigment or eyes Shadow
mix up and you have a brand new and
unique lip gloss in second so yeah never
throw away a lip
gloss even if you're bored of a
particular color that you own you can
always revamp it and make a completely
different product out of it plus mixing
up different makeup products is so much
fun makes me feel like a little lap
scientist most of us girls have that
special bond with glit it's like we
connect on a level that some people just
can't understand the world without
glitter would be a boring Place glitter
is just so sparkly magical and beautiful
until we try to put it on the face then
it just becomes a big old mess glitter
all over the face on our clothes
everywhere I hate glitter luckily
there's an epic life hack that will make
the glitter stay exactly where you put
it all you need is any kind of lip gloss
open it up and apply a very th layer on
the lids or wherever you want to apply
the glitter now it's time to take the
star of the show glitter the lovely the
gorgeous the most beautiful thing in the
world okay I'm going to stop I'm using
this pinky holographic Stripes but any
glitter will work pick some of these
magic Sparkles onto a flat brush and
gently tap it on the lid now look at
that the glitter stays exactly where you
put it no mess whatsoever my first eye
is done and as you can see my face is
not covered with glitter Fallout which
totally happens when you're not using a
lip gloss
underneath
now look at this Perfection on the eyes
this hack is seriously a lifes savior
when it comes to epic eye makeup looks
great for a date night out with your
friends or you can totally rock this on
a daily basis because you go girl you
can do the thing anyway I hope this life
hack will give you the courage to open
the glitter container more often because
now you know that glitter and mess don't
come as a couple the lip gloss hack is
so potent that it even works with beads
these little beads would never stay on
the lids but when you apply some lip
gloss underneath they just won't budge
isn't this amazing you can basically
stick on the lids whatever you want the
lip gloss has you
covered some mascaras have two sides a
black and a white one which is a primer
if you're like me then you almost never
use it what who has time for this
instead of throwing away this white
mascaras you can actually use them to
create amazing colored mascaras that's
right how cool are these all you need is
an ey shadow in whatever color you like
I chose blue because blue is my favorite
color scrip some of that pigment on a
piece of paper how pretty is this blue
color it will make the lashes look
amazing if you get some bigger chunks
like I did you can crush them into
smaller pieces with a toothpick take
your white mascara primer and open it up
I made a little paper funnel which I'm
placing in the opening now I can pour
the eyes Shadow into the mascara tube
you really don't need much eyeshadow to
color up your mascara so don't worry
about wasting it there we go our blue
mascara is all ready to use see how
pretty it looks and it works amazing
just make sure that you're using quite
pigmented eyeshadows or loose pigments
this will make your lashes look super
nice and colored look at my crazy lashes
I also made another mascara using purple
Shadow I love how you can make a mascara
in any possible color out there these
colored mascaras are perfect for parties
they're so fun for all of us who like
playing with makeup and experimenting
with different looks my purple mascara
turned out just as amazing as the blue
one I really need to try making a hot
pink and green one I bet they will look
awesome this DIY life hack is so quick
and easy plus it's really fun to make
and your lashes will be slaying love
it
what girl doesn't like having bright
colored lashes lips right I love them
but sometimes I'm absolutely fed up with
my lipstick smearing
everywhere I'm never wearing you
again to avoid these awkward situations
you can actually make your own DIY lip
tattoo using only two ingredients you
need a peel of face mask and food
coloring start by squeezing a small
amount of face mask into a little pot
make sure you're using a peel of face
mask otherwise you're not going to get
the same tattoo effect grab some food
coloring using a toothpick and mix it in
the face mask here I'm using red you
really don't need much food coloring for
this a drop is more than enough because
this stuff is potent I want to try all
the possible colors that I have so I'm
making a green orange and blue lip
tattoos as
well
okay all of them are ready which one
should I go for let's choose a classic
red take a bit of this red gel on a
brush and apply it all over those lips
it looks so glossy and epic but this is
just a temporary look because we're
going to be peeling it off in a few
minutes when your lips are all covered
you need to give the tattoo some time to
dry how much this takes it depends on
how thick layer you applied but after a
few minutes it should be ready yay my
tattoo is dry so I can peel it off this
is so weirdly satisfying the tattoo
gives A really lovely red color that
looks completely natural as you were
born with such pretty Rosy
lips and the best part no prints on the
tissue or even on the glass I think this
is so useful especially for School
sports activities or other occasions
when you don't have time checking up
whether you have lipstick on your teeth
I'm going to quickly show you the
swatches of other lip tattoo colors as
well now you can of course make crazy
blue or green lips but these are so
useful for other things too for example
you can draw little stars or Hearts as
temporary tattoos or you can even make a
fake teardrop tattoo using a blue color
these are so much fun to play with I
mean look at these awesome
colors and they survived the tissue test
as well no smearing whatsoever and don't
worry the color won't stay there forever
it stayed on me for a day and then it
got wrapped
away getting bored of the same old
eyeshadow look that you wear all the
time and no worries this life hack will
help you slay the ey Shadow game in
seconds all you need is a nail art tape
or just just a normal Scotch tape if
you're using the Scotch tape cut it in
Stripes using scissors with the help of
these tape pieces you can now create
awesome eyeshadow
designs I decided to stick four tape
strips on each of the lids vertically
and diagonally like that when you're
finished with your tape design all you
have to do is apply any eyeshadow of
your choice I went for a navy blue on
the outer corners and yellowy green
shade on the inner part of my lid you
can apply your ey Shadow with a brush or
using fingers I like using fingers when
I want the Shadows to be brighter and
more opaque when you're done simply
remove all the tapee strips and reveal
your eyeshadow Masterpiece wherever you
had the tape you get a stripe of bare
skin which makes an epic contrast with
the
eyeshadow like look at that isn't it
insanely awesome such an amazing eyes
shadow look that doesn't require any
makeup skills and not even a makeup
brush I think this is a great idea for a
party or any other special occasion I
bet all your friends will be asking you
how on Earth did you do that also be
creative with your designs you can make
horizontal lines triangles or even a
hashtag sign that would look so
epic I could wear this one but why am I
so pale I wish I faked them yesterday I
have an idea take a normal body lotion
and a golden eyeshadow or pigment to
make your very own DIY body bronzer
squeeze some body lotion into the pot
grab a golden pigment or eyeshadow and
pour some of it in as well give it a
good stir to combine the two ingredients
and that's pretty much it you can now
apply this body bronzer and it will give
your skin the most beautiful sunus glow
you can also add in Shimmer and you're
going to shine girl trust me instant
body bronzers can be very pricey while
you can make your DIY version for cheap
and it works just as
great matte lipsticks have been very
popular lately how wouldn't they be
they're super pigmented and they don't
smudge however they can be very drying
and after half an hour we end up looking
like this give your lips a break from
all that dryness with an extremely
moisturizing thin Ed lip balm which only
requires two ingredients a Vaseline and
food coloring squeeze some Vaseline into
a lip balm pot grab your food coloring
and take some product out using a
toothpick stir it into the Vaseline to
get a pretty red balm optionally you can
also add some flavoring I'm using
strawberry extract so that my lip balm
will smell amazing too mix it again put
the lid on and since packaging is
important I also decided to place on a
little hard sticker voila we got
ourselves an amazing moisturizing tinted
lip bulm in like 30 seconds I regularly
put f on my lips every evening and now I
can use it during the day as well it
makes my lips super soft and it gives
them a nice Rosy color and not to forget
it smells like strawberries especially
in the winter when our skin gets extra
dry this lip balm is the must
have I always run out of makeup products
when I need them the most luckily an
eyeliner can be easily replaced by a
usual coloring pencil you can use black
or just any other color of coloring
pencils yep get ready for some crazy ey
liner looks come on I'll show you first
you need to fill a glass with warm water
pop your coloring pencils in with a tip
facing down wait for about a minute and
you're ready to use your pencils as
eyeliners warm water softens the pencil
making it creamy and very pigmented just
like an eyeliner make sure to use
non-toxic pencils when doing this and
keep in mind that pencils are not made
to draw on skin every day you can use
this hack as an emergency when you run
out of eyeliner or for a special
occasion when you want to make that
crazy eyeliner look as you can see I
made the rainbow eyeliner ler using red
green blue orange and white
pencils this hack works so well it's
almost incredible I mean you can see the
color payoff it's crazy all the
different colors are working like magic
even better than many of the eyeliners I
own I'm truly
impressed
gosh I'm so late okay
brows right brow
gel too late every second counts when
getting ready in the morning right to
save you some precious time you can
transform your two-step brow routine
into a One Quick Step routine make your
own tinted brow gel all you need is a
clear brow gel and some shadow that you
use to fill in your brows scrape some of
that shadow onto a piece of paper I like
to combine dark and light color to get
the perfect eyebrow shade for
me you can make a funnel from a piece of
paper and tape to help you pour the
brown Shadow into the tube I'm also
using a toothpick to push the product
down lastly we have to remove the funnel
put the little plastic lid back in the
opening and we're all done you can shake
the bottle a little bit to help mix the
gel with the brown Shadow and you're
ready to use your DIY tinted brow gel
this thing works so well I was honestly
surprised when I tried it for the first
time I know you can also buy a tinted
brow gel in store but normally they only
have two versions light or dark my brows
are somewhere in between and I love how
I can mix up the perfect shade for
myself wo how did you do that oh it's an
epic hack I'll show you okay this makeup
hack may not be something that you use
every day for school or work but it's
just so cool that I had to include it
I'll show you an easy way to make a
gorgeous mermaid makeup I started with
coloring the lips in white white base
will give a beautiful contrast to the
colors which I'll apply later now for
the part take some fishnet tights and
pull them on your head like this I know
it looks scary but we only need this
temporarily let's start with lips di a
small brush in any eyes shadow of your
choice and apply it on the lips make
sure to tap the brush on the lips
instead of swiping it back and forth
this will make sure we don't ruin the
fishnet design we're going for for the
lips I decided to combine dark blue
light blue purple and pink colors I'm
now switching to a bigger flat brush and
I'm going to apply light blue on my
cheeks and temples again use tapping
motion instead of swiping back and forth
lastly I'm going in with pink and I'm
applying that below the blue if you want
to create a pretty gradient between the
blue and pink just tap some of that pink
over the blue when you're happy with
your design pull the tights off your
face and look at this epicness I mean
you need absolutely no makeup skills and
you can create something so gorgeous of
course this could be perfect for
Halloween or masquerade makeup but I
think it's an amazing party makeup too
if you use the usual blush colors like
pink or Peach and Rosy or red on the
lips you actually get that subtle
fishnet pattern that looks so beautiful
and not over the top at all you don't
need to spend a ton of money on makeup
products when there's so much you can do
from what you already have and you don't
need to be a makeup artist to create
awesome makeup looks either all you need
is an open mind and some epic life hacks
I hope you find these ideas helpful and
we'll try some of them out with all
these epic life hacks you're going to
slay that makeup game for sure give the
video some love if you enjoyed it and
tell me in the comments what is your
favorite makeup product right now mine
is probably concealer because it's just
like magic it erases all the
imperfections thank you so much for
watching guys I love you and I'll see
you soon bye there's so much more you
can do with makeup when you start
thinking outside the box be creative be
curious and have a lot of fun
experimenting fear take
over my life
not what